Miami Magma is a science fiction, action, tv movie
film directed by Todor Chapkanov.
Antoinette Vitrini, a volcanologist, confirms her theory of a long-dormant
underground volcano after an offshore-drilling rig bursts into flames.
Now, she must stop catastrophic amounts of magma from
pumping out right under Miami, Florida.
Antoinette Vitrini, played by Rachel Hunter.
Jacob Capilla, played by Brad Dourif.
Shauna, played by Stacey Asaro.
Brandon Rice, played by Griff Furst.
Dr. Brad Turner, played by J.D. Evermore.
Annie, played by Crystal Rivers.
Rachel Hunter (born 8 September 1969) is a New Zealand model, actress, and the
host of Imagination Television's Rachel Hunter's Tour of Beauty.
She has appeared on several magazine covers, including Vogue, Elle, Rolling Stone,
Sports Illustrated, Playboy, Cosmopolitan, and  Harper's Bazaar.
She has been on the cover of the Sports Illustrated Swimsuit Issue twice: in 1994 (alongside
Kathy Ireland and Elle Macpherson) and in 2006 (alongside six other models).
The film explores themes of beach, miami, florida,
volcano, burned alive, conspiracy.
The tone is thought_provoking.